

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a Full Stack web developer specialized in the PERN stack (PostgreSQL, Express, ReactJs, NodeJs) but always interested in learning and researching new tools and technologies.

I am a committed, constant and organized person when it comes to carrying out the objectives that are proposed to me, being able to integrate and adapt to different types of work teams.

#### CONTACT

Iorenzopedropodio@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/lorenzo-podio



github.com/LorenzoPodio

### **LENGUAGES**

Spanish: native

English: upper intermediate

## **EDUCATION**

#### Henry

Professional training bootcamp as a Full Stack Web Developer in Full-time mode starting November 2021 and ending in March 2022

### Technological National University - F.R.C.

Technical higher Technical Programming. 14/21 Subjects approved so far.

#### **Languages University - UNC**

Intermediate English level, equivalent to level B1, according to the levels of the Common European Framework of Reference for Languages.

#### Instituto Nuestra Madre de la Merced (HighSchool)

Oriented Bachelor in Humanities - Specialty: Social Sciences.

# LORENZO **PODIO**

## **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

## **SKILLS & TOOLS**

As a Full Stack Developer I have skills on handling the following languages and tools:

- JavaScript
- HTMI
- CSS

- React
- Redux
- Nodels

- Express
- Sequelize
- PostgreSQL

- Git
- Tailwind
- lava

- TypeScript
- Spring boot
- GitHub

## **EXPERIENCE**

## ExcursionApp (Academic)

App excursions e-commerce, Feb 2022 - Mar 2022

Technologies: •JavasScript •React •Context hook •Tailwind •NodeJs •Express •PostgreSQL •Sequelize •AuthO •MercadoPago •MapBox-GL-JS

## DogsApp (Academic)

Wiki app about dogs, Jan 2022 - Feb 2022

Technologies: •JavasScript •React •Redux •CSS Puro •NodeJs Express •PostgreSQL •Sequelize

### **GTrans S.R.L.**

Full Stack Developer, Aug 2020 - Oct 2021

I performed FrontEnd and BackEnd development tasks using the following tools: •JavasScript •Angular •TypeScript •Bootstrap •Java Spring boot •PostgreSQL

## OTHER FORMATIONS

#### Educación IT:

HTML5: Fundamentos de una pagina web.

## **Udemy:**

- GIT + GitHub: Todo un sistema de Control de
- Angular: El mejor curso de Angular. De Cero a Experto!

#### EF Set:

The achieved English level is 71/100 on the EF SET score scale and C2 Proficient according to the Common European Framework of Reference (CEFR).